<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">News</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">"Strategies "</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello</string>
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>
    <string name="theme">Themes</string>
    <string name="light_theme">Light</string>
    <string name="dark_theme">Dark</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="russian">Russian</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="menu_favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_prognoses">"Forecasts "</string>
    <string name="curse_change">Exchange rate change in % for:</string>
    <string name="market_stat">Brief market statistics</string>
    <string name="sort">Sorting:</string>
    <string name="list_settings">List settings</string>
    <string name="website">Website</string>
    <string name="source_code">Source code</string>
    <string name="market_stats">Market statistics:</string>
    <string name="price">Price:</string>
    <string name="total_supply">"Gen. offer "</string>
    <string name="max_supply">Max. offer</string>
    <string name="market_cap_full">Market cap.</string>
    <string name="market_cap_small">MC</string>
    <string name="main">Main</string>
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="perc_1h">% for 1h.</string>
    <string name="perc_1d">% for 1d.</string>
    <string name="perc_7d">% for 7d.</string>
    <string name="rang">Rang</string>
    <string name="price_dialog">Price</string>
    <string name="h1">1h</string>
    <string name="d1">1d</string>
    <string name="d7">7d</string>
    <string name="terms">Terms</string>
    <string name="altcoin_title">Altcoin</string>
    <string name="bitcoin_title">Bitcoin</string>
    <string name="blockchain_title">Blockchain</string>
    <string name="bulls_title">Bulls</string>
    <string name="flats_title">Flat</string>
    <string name="gap_title">Gap</string>
    <string name="dump_title">Dump</string>
    <string name="green_title">Green candle</string>
    <string name="inside_title">Inside</string>
    <string name="cryptowallet_title">Cryptocurrency</string>
    <string name="kits_title">Whales</string>
    <string name="red_title">Red candle</string>
    <string name="bears_title">Bears</string>
    <string name="otskok_title">Rebound</string>
    <string name="pump_title">Pump</string>
    <string name="hand_title">Shoulder</string>
    <string name="sliv_title">Drain</string>
    <string name="toTheMoon_title">To the Moon</string>
    <string name="shitcoin_title">Shitcoin</string>
    <string name="shitcoin">"unattractive cryptocurrency for investment. "</string>
    <string name="toTheMoon">"a sharp increase in the rate of cryptocurrencies (“flight to the moon”). "</string>
    <string name="sliv">"mass sale of cryptocurrencies. "</string>
    <string name="hand">"a loan that a broker can provide to a client to purchase securities backed by assets held in the client's account. Although credit can be provided not only in cash, but also in the form of securities, this term is usually used to refer to long positions opened on credit. Shoulder width is measured in relation to the size of the client account. For example: leverage of 2 to 1 means the possibility of obtaining 2 dollars of credit for 1 dollar of existing assets. "</string>
    <string name="pump">"mass purchase of cryptocurrency, aimed at artificial appreciation. "</string>
    <string name="otskok">"a phenomenon that usually occurs when a stock price falls (grows) sharply, when the price reaches a strong support (resistance) level, leads to an increase in buying (selling). As a result, the fall (growth) is temporarily suspended and the price rises (falls) somewhat from the levels reached, as if bouncing off like a ball. Then the movement of quotes resumes in the direction preceding the rebound. If such a continuation of the movement does not occur, then the rebound turns into a reversal. Unlike bounce, the term \"dead cat jump\" only refers to the situation where the bounce occurs during cushioning. "</string>
    <string name="bears">"these are traders who play on the downside of the price and deliberately reduce it to a minimum. "</string>
    <string name="red">"a sharp drop in the cryptocurrency rate, indicated in red on the chart. "</string>
    <string name="kits">"these are key exchange players who own a large amount of cryptocurrency and influence the market. "</string>
    <string name="cryptowallet">"this is a kind of digital currency, accounting for internal units of account of which is provided by a decentralized payment system operating in a fully automatic mode. "</string>
    <string name="inside">"important information that can affect stock quotes, but is available at the time of its appearance only to a narrow circle of people - insiders. Insiders use this information to their advantage until it becomes available to other participants. "</string>
    <string name="green">"the rapid growth of the cryptocurrency rate, marked in green on the chart. "</string>
    <string name="dump">"intentionally selling cryptocurrencies in gigantic quantities to artificially depreciate "</string>
    <string name="gap">"a significant gap, a jump in quotes. Usually happens between the price of the morning open and the previous evening close of the market. Occurs in the event of a change in the market situation during the time until the auction was held. "</string>
    <string name="flats">"Unlike a trend, a sideways movement characterizes the movement of the market without a clearly defined direction. Quotes move as if sideways, flat - smooth (eng.). However, a really even sidewall is quite rare. "</string>
    <string name="bulls">traders playing on the increase in the prices of crypto-currencies</string>
    <string name="blockchain">"a decentralized database that is simultaneously stored on many computers connected to each other on the Internet. The word \"blockchain\" is translated from English as \"chain of blocks\". "</string>
    <string name="bitcoin">"the name of the first cryptocurrency. "</string>
    <string name="altcoin">"it is any cryptocurrency launched after bitcoin. Simply put, altcoins, of which there are already hundreds of varieties, act as improved alternatives to bitcoin. "</string>
    <string name="gold">"The golden cross and the death cross is a pretty exciting cryptocurrency trading strategy, and you need to understand both of these terms in order to implement it correctly. The golden cross is basically defined as the time at which the short-term average of a particular cryptocurrency crosses the long-term average. The short-term average is usually defined as the 50-day average, and the long-term average as the 200-day average.  On the other hand, the death cross is the exact opposite of the golden cross and is defined as the moment when the short-term average drops below the long-term average.  Confirmation of the presence of these trends is carried out by analyzing changes in trading volume. Some traders also use other indicators such as RSI and MACD, but volume is considered one of the best indicators.  The strategy revolves around buying at the golden cross and selling at the death cross. "</string>
    <string name="scalping">"Scalping is the execution of small trades with a minimum duration of time with a small profit.  The length of time should be short, ideally no more than an hour. The biggest asset for scalpers is volume; the number of transactions is more important than the profit from one transaction. Scalpers will never seek big profits and cannot afford to wait for the market to turn around to mitigate losses.  Scalping should never be done at uncertain times and the best market to scalp is a calm market with limited volatility. "</string>
    <string name="obr_torg">"Reverse trading is considered one of the best trading strategies for cryptocurrencies and is based on a change in the general trend in the market. To understand this in detail, the strategy is to find the exact moment when the trend is about to change. If the coin has been bullish for a while, the reverse trader will look for a time when he will reverse the trend and bet on it.  Another interesting version of reverse trading is trading by forecasting the high/low of the day and making money from that forecast. The risk associated with this strategy is the general risk of incorrectly forecasting the turnaround time. "</string>
    <string name="buy_and_ud">"The subtleties of managing the cryptocurrency rate If a trader expects to make a profit in months, then the best option would be to follow the steps prescribed in the Buy and Hold strategy. In fact, the scheme is very simple: you need to buy the selected currency and keep it in your wallet until the moment when it rises in price very much.  To follow this tactic, a trader must have nerves of steel and know the market very well. The point here is that almost any digital currency is adjusted in price in the long term, which often results in a drawdown of the exchange rate. And, naturally, many have a desire to sell the purchased coins in order to return the money invested for fear of losing a large amount.  To avoid such a temptation and the loss of possible good profits in the future, the initial determination of the desired price will help. And at the moment of reaching the desired value, the cryptocurrency must be immediately sold. "</string>
    <string name="diapozon">"For such trading, it is necessary to take into account the RSI indicator chart. It demonstrates the overbought (upper border) and oversold (lower border) zones, which serve as reference points for the trader to trade. At the moment when buying and selling go beyond the bottom line, the asset is in the overbought zone. This means that there are fewer buyers than sellers. As one of the options for behavior - to enter into deals on the longs. If the asset is in the oversold zone - that is, beyond the upper limit - then, on the contrary, there are fewer sellers than buyers. Here, as one of the many options for behavior - go into short positions or sell an asset. "</string>
    <string name="arbitr">"The arbitrage trading strategy is simple and conceptually very clear. Simply put, an asset is bought when the price is low and sold when the price is up.  For example, arbitrage trading in the bitcoin market would be when you buy bitcoin for 60,000 USD on one cryptocurrency exchange and then sell it on another cryptocurrency exchange platform for 62,000 USD. In this example, a trader will be able to make a profit of 2,000 USD simply by buying and selling cryptocurrency. It is important to note that this is just an example and in the real world a price difference of 2000 USD will probably not exist between cryptocurrency exchanges. "</string>
    <string name="sovets">"To avoid obvious mistakes and fatal loss of money investments, experienced stock market players recommend following the following rules: Do not go against market trends. Buy as low as possible and sell high. Do not trade on the last funds. Do not invest the entire amount of the deposit in one transaction. Be sure to record all your transactions, that is, keep a diary in which to record all your transactions with subsequent analysis of errors in order to avoid their repetition in the future. "</string>
    <string name="arbitr_title">"Arbitration "</string>
    <string name="diapozon_title">"Range trading "</string>
    <string name="buy_and_ud_title">Purchase and hold</string>
    <string name="obr_torg_title">"Reverse trade "</string>
    <string name="scalping_title">"Scalping "</string>
    <string name="gold_title">"Golden cross and death cross "</string>
    <string name="sovets_title">VALUABLE ADVICE</string>
    <string name="show_text">"This is solely the opinion of the author. He can be biased and biased. "</string>
    <string name="dont_ask_again">"Don't show next time "</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="d30">1m</string>
    <string name="y1">1y</string>
</resources>